As the sun climbs higher every day,
随着太阳日渐升高
it warms the ice.
暖化了冰层
Soon, the emperors' frozen world will start to melt away.
帝企鹅的冰封世界  很快就要开始融化了
For the last few weeks,
在最后几周的时间里
the mother and father have taken it in turn to feed their offspring.
妈妈和爸爸轮流喂养后代
But its growing appetite will soon force both parents to go away fishing at the same time.
然而小企鹅的胃口越来越大 不久之后  父母只好同时离开去捕鱼
Now it's time to encourage the month-old chicks
是时候鼓励一个月大的小企鹅
to stand on their own two feet.
自己站起来了
Sometimes, it takes a well-timed kick.
有时候需要适时的一踢
Now, both parents can head off to sea to go fishing.
现在父母都能离开 前往大海捕鱼了
For the first time, the chicks will have to face the elements
小企鹅们  第一次脱离父母的保护
without a parent to protect them.
只能独自面对大自然
Other adults certainly won't look after them.
其他成年企鹅肯定不会照顾它们
So, lone chicks gather together for comfort.
于是孤独的小企鹅们聚在一起 相互取暖